yarn run v1.22.19
$ next lint
Attention: Next.js now collects completely anonymous telemetry regarding usage.
This information is used to shape Next.js' roadmap and prioritize features.
You can learn more, including how to opt-out if you'd not like to participate in this anonymous program, by visiting the following URL:
https://nextjs.org/telemetry

info Visit https://yarnpkg.com/en/docs/cli/run for documentation about this command.
